I don't like Su-jin.
The person I like…
is you.
BASED ON WEBTOON TRUE BEAUTY
BY YAONGYI
Ju-kyung.
Why are you running away?
I don't know, it just happened.
But…
it's really me?
Yes.
It's you.
That doesn't make sense.
You're joking, right?
Is this a hidden camera prank?
Is everyone hiding somewhere?
Or are you pity liking me?
Or maybe I'm dreaming?
It's none of those.
Then…
you really like…
Am I not allowed to?
Goodness.
I'm so nervous…
I can't even speak.
I'm nervous too.
I was going to tell you
while giving you this.
Look.
I got all the steps mixed up.
So what about you?
Sorry?
I'm nervous and I have butterflies.
What do you think that means?
- What does it mean?
- It means I really like you.
I like you. I like you a lot.
I dream about you
and I've thought about you all day.
I'm super lazy,
but I've been waking up before my alarm
to go to school early and see you.
And when I see you, my heart…
Anyway,
that's my answer.
Lim Ju-kyung.
I still can't believe it.
I'm not dreaming, am I?
It hurts.
Su-jin!
Who is that?
What do you mean? It's Ju-kyung!
Right, I don't have makeup on.
Ju-kyung.
But why do you
go to such lengths to hide it?
Once…
I asked the kids who bullied me.
About why they hated me so much.
Because you are ugly.
They said it's because I'm ugly.
They simply didn't like my face.
But once I put makeup on,
kids looked at me differently.
They even talk to me first,
and I could make friends easily.
That's when I thought,
I could never
take this mask off.
It must have been difficult for you,
always worrying about people finding out.
If they find out about my bare face,
I'm so scared that they'll curse at me
and turn on me.
I'm really lame, aren't I?
The ones who made you feel this way
are way lamer.
Don't you ever think that way again,
got it?
You said you don't want
the others to find out.
How do we get you inside?
Get up.
What?
Get in.
Let's go.
Let's go!
- We're going in like this?
- Yes.
I really went back and forth
between heaven and hell.
I'm grateful it was Su-jin at any rate.
LEE SOO-HO
Good night.
LIM JU-KYUNG
My finger slipped.
You too.
- What's up with Lee Soo-ho?
- Did he just smile?
I've never seen him smile before.
He's so handsome.
On average…
Throw it away.
Since when do we exchange drinks?
Throw it away. Did you not hear me?
That was rude.
What is it?
Doesn't she know
how expensive strawberries are?
Have you not told her yet?
You're killing me.
Man.
Seo-jun, aren't you going back
to your classroom?
- No, I'm not.
- I see.
Then where should I sit?
- Hurry up and go!
- I don't want to. You go.
Hey, I can't change my class on a whim.
- Come on. Get up.
- Right.
Won't you help me? Come on!
That's right.
Let's go to the sauna
after studying this weekend.
What do you say?
The sauna?
I don't really want to.
Come on, let's go. It'll be fun, right?
Let's go together.
Well, I…
The sauna? No thanks. I hate getting hot.
Fine, then. Jeez.
What's that?
He always eats alone.
Is he close with her?
He's having lunch with Ju-kyung?
There goes my appetite!
Hey, you only had one bite.
Maybe she's on a diet.
That traitor.
She's trying to get even prettier.
She's downright avoiding you, isn't she?
She must know you like her
and is giving you the cold shoulder.
Savior Soo-ho has already been rejected
before he confesses.
Ju-kyung? What happened?
TRULY, YOU'RE SO ANNOYING
"So annoying."
"A butthead."
Poor bastard.
This one is my favorite,
but you can have it.
TRASH INCINERATION AREA
- Gosh, it's Soo-ho.
- He's so tall.
- He's so handsome
- Seriously.
Get down.
Do we really have to do this?
- Of course.
- Why?
What do you mean why?
Haven't you heard?
After you said you liked someone,
even if a girl brushed shoulders with you,
the delinquents who like you
drag them to the rooftop.
If word gets out that I'm dating you…
Hey.
Are you the girl who flirted with Soo-ho?
What?
No. It wasn't me.
Look at her shaking her tail like a fox.
Grab that fox!
No, I didn't flirt with him!
How does that make sense?
- It makes perfect sense.
- So you want to keep this up?
Well,
I'm going to tell Su-jin and Su-ah,
of course.
I just feel a bit shy.
How do I tell them that you're…
my boyfriend?
But I am your boyfriend.
It's weird.
That word doesn't sound right to me.
You know one-on-one counseling
starts next week, right?
- Yes.
CAREER INTEREST SURVEY
It's almost a spy operation.
No one from our school is around, right?
We're an hour away from school.
No one would come here.
But still.
Thank you for coming.
Welcome! Please follow me.
Would you mind a table in an open area?
Somewhere not visible
to security cameras or onlookers.
A secretive, hidden spot, please.
Okay.
Then come this way.
Those young kids are already so demanding.
Please take your time with your menu
and let me know.
Can we get the couple's set?
You know, the menu only for couples?
That one, please.
We're a couple, you see.
All right.
A couple's set? Got it.
A couple.
We can act like a couple
now that no one's around.
You won't even let me
talk to you at school.
It doesn't feel like we're dating.
It feels like we are to me.
It really hit me when I changed this.
What name do you have me saved as?
- In mine--
- Lim Ju-kyung.
- That's my name.
- Yes.
- What about it?
- Well…
My name…
is pretty.
BOYFRIEND
Enjoy.
Do they only give one fork
for a couple's set?
Why is that?
Open up.
You're so cute.
To do that.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Here.
I'm sorry! I forgot your…
Enjoy.
What?
Ju-kyung?
Get down!
Hyun-kyu, what brought you this far out?
This place is famous.
- We come to places like this.
- Right.
What brought you out here and with whom?
I came here alone.
You came here alone
and ordered a couple's set?
It was a decent set.
- She is right about that.
- That's right.
I see.
I guess you can eat more than I thought.
Enjoy your meal.
- Halt.
- No!
Excuse me, sir.
- Hey.
- What?
Let's protect her privacy.
- Okay.
- You're quite the gentleman.
Well, I guess your boyfriend is quite shy?
What do you mean by boyfriend?
Do you want me to lift it up?
It was nice meeting you,
Ju-kyung's boyfriend.
Next time, let's talk face-to-face.
Well, enjoy your date with your boyfriend.
- Go, Ju-kyung!
Well, that was too close.
An hour away is still dangerous.
We could run into our classmates again,
so I'll be off first.
I brought you here to show you something.
Let's see it, then leave.
Aren't you…
a fan of hers?
It's Selena!
What do I do?
For makeup on acne-prone skin,
you all use high-coverage products, right?
- Yes.
- That's right.
However, gentle products
like this tone-up cream
work much better to cover skin irritation.
Don't forget it.
She's awesome.
Okay, here's a question for you.
I have giveaways, so please pay attention.
While prepping your face
before foundation,
this product can help you apply
the foundation evenly without concealer.
What is this product?
Me!
Over there, you in the brown jacket.
A primer.
A primer? A primer.
That is correct!
The person who got the answer,
come up and claim your prize.
- I'm so jealous.
- What's that?
I got this!
Excuse me…
I'm your biggest fan.
Could I get your autograph?
To remember this by?
Wait a moment. Here it is.
It's a long story,
but you gave me a whole new life.
My friends say I'm good at makeup,
and I learned it all
from watching your videos.
Thank you.
It sucks.
Excuse me?
I said, it sucks.
If you learned makeup from my videos,
how could you pick this shade
for your lips?
Different intensities feel distinct,
even if they're all the same warm tone.
A subtle difference in the shade
can ruin the balance of a whole look.
Here, how does that look?
If you're not going to do it right,
don't say you learned makeup from me.
Thank you. I'll try to do better.
But still, you are doing better
than when I first started.
Don't get discouraged and keep on trying.
Are you that happy?
Yes, I'm so happy.
I couldn't tell the difference.
You did better than her if you asked me.
Hey, I'm nothing compared to Selena.
I couldn't be like her even if I tried.
Why not?
She wasn't an expert
when she first started out.
But still, you are doing better
than when I first started.
Come on.
Still.
I guess you liked seeing Selena
more than our first date.
What?
Nothing.
You haven't closed yet.
- Did you have customers this late?
- Hey, Ju-kyung!
Why are you roaming about so late?
Did you have dinner yet, Ju-kyung?
I did have dinner.
Guess who I saw today?
I saw Selena!
Selena? Who's that?
- She's a famous makeup artist--
- The one who does makeup for celebrities?
She has a tough job just like me.
There's no money coming in,
but always money going out.
Taking care of a family of five
is incredibly difficult.
If only we still had our apartment.
Is business not doing well lately?
It's not like how it used to be.
I need to make it work
until you all graduate college.
I'll get going then.
Hey!
Take this out on your way out.
It stinks.
And do the dishes when you get home.
COLUMBUS PARK SPOTTED
We'll get fruit flies otherwise.
Ju-young is at home.
You should have asked him.
I've always wanted this.
It's so soft.
CAREER INTEREST SURVEY
So what if I have an interest?
It's not as if my interest
will get me there.
Which college should I choose?
MAKEUP ARTIST LICENSE COURSE
1.5 MILLION WON PER MONTH
1.5 million won?
It's too expensive to even dream about it.
What's going on? Did you drink again?
No.
Alcohol…
drank me.
What's going on with her lately?
- Take off your shoes first.
- Throw them out.
Hello?
Hee-kyung.
Where are you?
I couldn't reach you at all.
My sister is asleep right now.
By the way, who is this?
I…
was her subordinate in the military.
Have a good night.
Salute!
- A subordinate in the military?
- Salute.
That voice sounded very familiar.
I have a headache.
Dad, where's my uniform?
- Here it is.
- Honey, get me some water.
Dad!
- Honey?
- I'm hungry.
Hey, have you guys seen your dad?
No.
Gosh, where did he go
early in the morning?
What's this?
TO MY DEAR FAMILY
I can't believe this!
- What is it?
- What?
To my dear family, Hyun-sook, kids,
I'm heading to Jeju Island
to catch Columbus Park.
I won't be heading back home
until I get him and my money back.
But don't you worry about me.
This is absolutely ridiculous!
Someone's enjoying her life.
Hey, wake up. The bus will be here soon.
Hey, Seo-jun.
Hey, do you fall asleep
just about anywhere?
You wouldn't know if you got kidnapped.
I'm heavy so that won't be possible.
I'm sorry about that.
Seriously?
I should have ignored you and left.
What am I doing, seriously?
What?
I see you're not riding
your motorcycle these days.
Is it because I told you not to?
What?
You should listen to your mother.
I'm sorry,
but I have a soft spot for a sick person,
so I have to take her side on this.
Hey, your mom's worried sick about it.
So why risk it and ride the motorcycle?
Do you think
I'm one to simply follow your orders?
I'm a very good son, you know.
I'm not riding it
since my mom told me not to.
The bus will arrive shortly.
The bus is here. Where are you going?
I'm going to run to school
to get some exercise. Why?
See you later.
What was that?
Gosh. What am I doing, really?
I'm sorry.
I won't be able to see you this evening.
Is something going on?
Mr. Han, if you're free this evening,
will you help me choose
a birthday present for the vice principal?
Excuse me?
I'm supposed to get it,
but I'm not sure what to get for a man.
Well, I'm no expert
in choosing gifts either.
I can accompany you.
I have to go to the department store
to get a present for my wife anyway.
Yes, hello?
Well then, Mr. Han. I'll see you later.
But…
Hey, Ju-kyung's here.
Limju, you have a boyfriend now?
How come you didn't tell me?
What school does he go to?
He's not in our school, is he? Tell me.
Who told you that?
I saw them at the K-Mall.
She hid him because
she didn't want us to see him.
Hey, I told you it wasn't like that.
Hey, why are you being so shy?
You got a boyfriend.
- So what?
- He's right.
You're overreacting too.
- Are you dating a celebrity or something?
- "A celebrity."
- Is she, though?
- Really?
Tell me. Who is it?
So you got a boyfriend?
No, it's not like that.
Then what are they talking about?
Man.
I told you to tell her how you feel,
you dum-dum!
What to do now?
What's wrong with you?
Don't act up, okay?
Hey!
Go back to your seats.
- Let's go.
LIM JU-KYUNG
Want to go to Prince Comics later?
BOYFRIEND
Sure.
Let's get instant noodles with egg too.
I forgot to ask. Send me the picture.
What picture?
The picture we took on the boat together.
AHN HYUN-KYU
BOYFRIEND
Why aren't you sending me the photo?
AHN HYUN-KYU
Ahn Hyun-kyu?
Darn it. Why him?
Hey, don't fall off.
UNREAD
He hasn't read it yet.
All right.
I just have to get rid of the evidence.
I can do it.
- Move forward!
- Just do it quickly!
Hey, Ju-kyung!
I'm sorry.
Hey, I told you not to do it like that!
- You should have done it right!
- You don't even make sense!
- Man, seriously.
- It's not my fault!
USE FINGERPRINT OR ENTER PIN
Okay, your Korean History teacher's here!
All right,
have a seat.
The Japanese Invasion of Korea in 1592,
the Imjin War.
What's a good way to memorize this?
I need to delete it
before he notices his phone's missing.
That should do the trick, right?
Fingerprint.
How do I get his fingerprint?
…the politics of that era…
Is Su-ah taking a class
on the science of sleep?
She wouldn't wake
even if someone took her.
- Cute.
- Seriously, 1592…
That's it.
Fall asleep.
The rest of you, focus up.
So you won't know what hits you.
Why is he suddenly studying so hard?
Come on, fall asleep.
What is she doing?
All right, you're falling asleep.
Falling asleep.
Red Sun!
Mark down the things
I said were important.
Awesome.
Okay, that's it for today.
I'll see you next time!
LIM JU-KYUNG
- What? Why do you have my phone?
- What?
I said why do you--
What is this about?
It's nothing.
Excuse me.
Seriously, what's up with her?
Gosh.
If Hyun-kyu found out about us,
the whole school…
No, even people from other schools
would know of it by now.
The rumors about the rooftop
must have really shaken you.
That too, but…
I'm afraid of people talking smack
when they learn of our relationship.
They'd wonder why a guy like you
would date a girl like me.
And what's wrong with you?
It's obvious.
I'm neither pretty
nor smart.
You are way out of my league.
You're enough.
You're enough just the way you are.
So don't say things like that.
PRINCE COMICS
At least this place
is free of our schoolmates.
- Want to meet up here from now on?
- Sure.
What is it?
Look who's here! Go-un!
Ju-kyung!
This place won't work either.
I'll call you later.
- Get home safe!
- Okay.
It's probably too young for him.
Should we exchange it?
They all look pretty similar to me.
Will you get up, please?
How did you…
Do you know this person?
Who…
- I'm Lim Hee-kyung.
- Right.
And who are you?
- I'm Lee Hye-lim.
- Indeed.
I'm his colleague.
For now.
Is that going to change in the future?
I guess colleagues these days
are quite intimate.
You meet outside of work
and fix his ties and stuff?
No. Not at all.
You've misread--
What's your relationship
with Mr. Han, then?
- Well…
- His girlfriend.
- Excuse me?
- What?
We're seeing each other.
- My ears aren't working…
- His girlfriend!
- Let's talk outside.
- I can't hear well.
We're dating! This guy is my man!
Can't you hear at all?
Jeez, what kind of…
Goodness.
You're Mr. Han's girlfriend?
So nice to meet you!
- Nice to meet you too.
- Sir, I'm sorry.
I'm going to head home.
But why?
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
What is it?
Jun-woo.
It's…
CAREER INTEREST SURVEY
HANKOOK UNIVERSITY COSMETOLOGY
What's with her?
Why is she sleeping all day?
She was up late
looking for a part-time job.
What? A part-time job?
She must have been really tired.
Hey, you dropped this.
Right, Kangsu.
Want to stop by the snack bar?
Kangsu!
Guys should hold girls like that.
Isn't that Soo-ho's?
Then I'll give it to him.
Have you seen Ju-kyung?
Ju-kyung asked me to bring this to you.
She asked you?
RESUME
- Is this your first job?
- Yes.
- I'm looking for someone with experience.
- I'll work hard if you train me.
Plenty of people can work hard.
The thing is,
I need someone who'll do well.
- I'm sorry.
- Well…
I understand.
I'm sorry. We already have a part-timer.
I guess it's not easy
to get a part-time job either.
BOYFRIEND
The person you are trying to reach
is unavailable…
Is he very busy?
A pervert!
What the heck?
- Seo-jun?
- What's this?
What are you doing here?
The same goes for you.
Why are you taking your clothes off
in the women's restroom?
Damn it!
You totally look like a model.
Are you doing a photo shoot?
Yes.
Bye.
What? Really?
Hey, Seo-jun!
A billion won?
Mr. Lee donated big this year.
That's why the hospital director
brought in the press
and made a big deal out of
giving him an appreciation plaque.
One might think that Lee Ju-hun
founded our hospital's cancer center.
- Hello!
- We kept you waiting, haven't we?
- I'm sorry.
- There's no need.
I invited you when you must be busy.
Soo-ho, it's been a while, right?
Hello, how have you been?
Okay, that was great just now. Edgy.
Now turn. Just once, that's it.
I'm moving in closer.
You look great. One, two.
Hey, the last two shots.
One, two, two, three.
Three, two… Okay.
It's perfect, Seo-jun.
Smile a bit more. One, two.
Look down. Here.
Okay. One, two.
Three, two. Right, just like that.
Go, one, two.
Okay! We got it.
Seo-jun, let's get you changed.
Great job.
What? You're still here?
Yes. It was exciting,
so I stayed and watched.
- Hold on. Are you Seo-jun's girlfriend?
- No, she's not.
- Hello.
- Hi.
If you have such a pretty friend…
Pretty, my foot.
- Hurry up and leave.
- Jeez. All right.
Wait.
What's your problem, kicking her out?
Excuse me, Seo-jun's friend?
Do you want to model for the day?
Actually, our female model didn't show up,
so I was in trouble.
- Me?
- Hey.
Can anyone be a model now?
I told you to leave!
We desperately need a model
to update our new items in time.
So, would you like to try it?
Well…
But I've never done
anything like this before…
You might do better
because you're a blank slate.
And since you're his friend,
I'll give you a better pay.
There's payment?
Then I want to try it!
- Hey!
- Awesome.
I heard you two are
in the same class this year.
I hope you take good care of him, Su-jin.
I keep telling him to move in with me,
but he won't listen.
Since we live apart,
looking after him isn't easy.
I will.
I can manage on my own
without a caretaker.
Don't you worry.
By the way,
Soo-ho looks more like you
with each passing day.
Have you thought about making him a star?
His grades are too good
for him to just be a celebrity.
Is that right?
As long as it's something Soo-ho likes,
I'll support whatever he chooses.
You can say that
since he does well on his own.
If I don't hold the reins for Su-jin,
she'll lose her senses and hit the bottom.
Compared to boys,
she lacks patience
and isn't as competitive.
That's why she always falls behind Soo-ho.
Your innate smarts do factor in, but…
We have a study session.
- You're leaving already?
- Yes, excuse us.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
Take care.
That's a little awkward.
No, don't do that.
Don't point at things.
Try acting natural, okay?
All right, one, two.
No, that's not it either.
- Try something natural.
- Something like this?
Out of the question. One, two.
No. Don't do that.
- Not the hair--
- Come on!
You're keeping her when she's this bad?
I haven't taken very many photos.
I'm so sorry.
That's only natural for a newbie.
He was the same. Right, Seo-jun?
Seo-jun, can you get close to her
and get things moving?
Act like you are really close, okay?
Okay, let's go! All right.
One, two, three.
That's it. Arms around his shoulders.
Okay, Seo-jun, smile. Go on.
We just need you to smile, Seo-jun.
Come on.
Hey, Han Seo-jun!
Why are you acting like an amateur?
It's not your first couple shoot.
Let's just stop, then.
It must be your empty stomach talking.
I'll get you something nice.
Let's take ten.
Let's take ten, guys.
Sure.
- I'm really bad, aren't I?
- No.
You're awful beyond imagination.
So tell him you can't do it and leave.
Are you being territorial? That's petty.
You should help me out.
I don't want to.
Is it because of the lights?
It's really hot in here.
- What are you doing?
- What?
I can't ruin a new dress.
- It's so hot.
- Jeez.
My face is too shiny.
Want me to dab your face?
What are you doing?
You've got some sweat on you too.
No thanks. Go sit over there.
Why not? I'm trying to
make you look good in the pictures.
I said, don't.
Does this come easy to you?
What does?
I'm a man too.
You're certainly a man and not a woman.
What's this?
That's what I wanted. Where's my camera?
Okay, great.
Let's go. Look this way.
Just like that, one, two.
Cooperate so we can wrap it up quickly.
You really are just reading.
Wasn't the study session just an excuse?
No, it wasn't.
But still, thank you.
My food wasn't going down back there.
Are you really
not moving in with your dad?
It sounded like he really wants you to.
We've lived apart for longer.
It'll only make things awkward.
It's comfortable right now.
Yours and mine…
What's wrong with our dads?
By the way,
nothing has happened since then?
- Did you get slapped--
- No, nothing happened.
Things will be calm
until the next report card.
Anyway, what gives?
You're worried about me?
What do you mean?
You've been talking more lately
as if you've regained some humanity.
Whatever.
MISSED CALL LIM JU-KYUNG
I missed a call.
BOYFRIEND
It's on me since it was
thanks to you I got paid.
- Why are you getting a part-time job?
- To pay for beauty school.
Beauty school?
While filling out
my career interest survey,
I thought about what I found interesting,
and makeup came to my mind.
My heart fluttered
when I did stage makeup for Go-un.
My sister
did look like a different person.
- Here's your tteokbokki.
- It's here!
Anyway,
you've had many girlfriends, haven't you?
Why do you ask?
What did you save her as in your phone?
Do guys not put much meaning into this?
Yes, they do.
I save my girlfriend's number
under something super sweet,
like my love, baby, or princess.
With hearts.
I see.
Right, I told you on our school trip…
I don't care. Don't tell me.
I'm dating Soo-ho.
You really don't listen.
I said, don't tell me.
I don't want to either.
But after crying about liking him
in front of you,
- how could I not say anything?
- I'm not congratulating you.
You're eating well.
Should I order one more?
Don't bother!
The others didn't seem to know.
Is this also a secret?
Yes, I think it'd be best for now.
And Soo-ho easily agreed to that?
Why do you ask?
If I had a girlfriend,
I'd want to show her off
and tell everyone.
That's how I'd feel, at least.
Get down.
Do we really have to do this?
I wonder if I hurt his feelings.
- Is it spicy?
- No.
It's perfect. I love it.
Are you going home now?
Look! Those kids go to our middle school.
I see.
I think you've gotten taller.
You used to be shorter than me
and would get beaten up.
When did you get so tall?
Still talking about our kindergarten days?
- Get home safe.
- Okay.
- I'll walk you home.
- Hello?
See you tomorrow.
We keep missing each other's calls.
I have heartburn.
Why did I shove all that in
when I can't even eat spicy food?
Eat.
Here.
What did you do today?
I interviewed for part-time jobs,
but I didn't get any of them.
Anyway, I made some money
for the first time ever.
I ran into Seo-jun somehow--
Sir?
Soo-ho?
"Sir"?
Who do you mean?
Just now…
I saw your…
You can't.
How can a person scam others
in a scam victims' group?
They asked us to go catch him as a group.
Then they ran off
with our flight and lodging fees.
They were very clever and organized.
It sounds like you fell for a sloppy scam.
No, they were…
Gosh. Whatever.
I talked big to my family
about how I won't return until I got him,
so how can I go back?
That's why you should
keep this a secret from Ju-kyung, okay?
She must be worried, so how could I?
- Let's just call her right--
- No, never!
If you tell her now,
I'll run away and never return.
Then what is your plan?
You said you're out of money now.
I'd rather freeze to death
sleeping on this cold floor
than go back home.
Not to mine, at least.
Okay.
What?
Well then, good night.
- What?
- I'll get going.
Soo-ho. Wait a moment.
- Your name means savior.
- That's right.
You have some saving to do.
Hey, Soo-ho, wait up.
You live here by yourself?
Mr. Lee sure must be busy.
You can take a shower here.
Soo-ho!
- Are you all right?
- I think I sprained my back. I can't move.
Help me up, please.
You can sleep here.
I'll sleep on the couch.
I can't possibly do that.
I can't be so brazen
to my daughter's friend.
I'll sleep outside,
so don't mind me,
and sleep here in comfort.
Good night then.
Soo-ho, thank you.
Thank you, Soo-ho.
The house looks seriously terrible
without Dad.
Hey, why don't you clean my room
while you're at it?
- Then I should start with you.
- That's disgusting!
There you go again!
I'll do the cleaning.
Leave it and come have some apples.
It's fine.
You must be tired after working all day.
I'm almost done.
- Like a lone flower blossoming
In a wide open field
I've protected the feeling of emptiness
Inside my heart
Like the sun coming out
- After heavy rain…
- …I've protected
- The feeling of emptiness…
- Hey!
Don't you sing that song.
- Don't sing it!
- What?
What's up with him?
Anyway, I wonder if your dad
is at least eating some food.
He's probably eating well
and sleeping well.
Mr. Lim?
Gosh, you startled me.
Did I wake you? I'm sorry.
What are you doing up this early?
Son Heung-min's playing, you see…
Right, I'd set an alarm for it.
You're his fan, then.
Shall we watch the second half together?
Mr. Lim.
After watching the first half highlights.
Looks good.
Here, have some.
I don't eat at this hour.
It's not the same with a game going on.
You'll regret it if you don't. Come on.
I'll eat it myself.
Okay then.
- You have no idea how good it is.
- He's just like Ju-kyung.
It looks so good.
It's so hot!
Hot!
- I burned my tongue.
- Here.
You should have slowed down.
You're quite sweet, Soo-ho.
The second half starts
- with Son Heung-min's kick-off!
- Son Heung-min!
Which team will advance to the final?
Yes. As we speak,
he quickly goes to score an equalizer
as the second half starts.
He crosses the ball early!
It falls short.
Son Heung-min gets it right away!
He doesn't hesitate
and uses his right foot. Shoot, goal!
Son Heung-min scores
just two minutes into the second half.
Soo-ho!
Soo-ho.
You barely had your breakfast.
Have this on the way.
Go enjoy your classes and come home later.
That's not it.
I'll have gone home by then.
Thanks for everything.
You're going home now, right?
I'll keep your secret just for today--
Okay. I'll be off
as soon as I finish the dishes.
I just need to be prepared mentally.
To get scolded by my wife.
He's so young but is so mature.
Is it because he had to grow up
without his mom?
Watch out for cars!
- Have fun at school!
- I'm off.
Let's go.
What are they teaching you
in P.E. class today?
- Soccer.
- Is that so?
That'll be fun.
What's wrong? Are you lost?
What?
Why do you continue
to roam around in my thoughts?
All right.
I'll give you a chance
to remain in my thoughts.
Well…
Go out with me.
Why?
Are you so overwhelmed
that you can't speak?
Really not funny.
"Really not funny"?
Here.
I used to work at this cafe,
and they're hiring a part-timer.
I already told them about you,
so visit them later.
Gosh.
Amazing. In one day?
Hey, thank you so much.
You're well-connected.
Great job! Excellent!
You're really great. Thank you.
- Ju-kyung.
- What?
Let's go.
Try to memorize the menu
as soon as possible.
Drink recipes are all posted here,
but until you learn them,
you'll take orders and do the dishes.
Got it.
Welcome.
I haven't cleaned the cups yet.
- Can you please wash the cups first?
- Yes, of course.
Hi, what can I get you?
Oh, no, are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Goodness.
These will be uploaded to the website.
They came out well, right?
JEONG-HUN
Why would he send me these?
He could've sent just a few.
WILL YOU DELETE THIS IMAGE?
DELETE
CANCEL, DELETE
CAFE OWNER
Yes, ma'am?
You decided to hire Ju-kyung?
Yes.
Thanks for introducing her.
Ju-kyung is here right now
getting trained.
Goodness. Did you get hurt, Ju-kyung?
What? She got hurt?
It barely touched me.
I'm all right. Really.
Ju-kyung.
Thank you.
Seo-jun!
Where's Ju-kyung?
She left a bit ago.
- Excuse me?
- Did you run here?
Have I gone mad?
Why did I run here?
Hey, where did you get the eyelash curler?
What's with that rude punk?
He didn't even apologize.
Are you all right?
Han Seo-jun?
I guess Hee-kyung is not here yet.
What about Ju-young?
Ju-young? He went to his math tutor.
What? He got a tutor?
He wanted to get better at math
so I got him a tutor.
You always say we don't have money.
You said you had no customers
and that things are rough.
Even if I have no money,
I need to provide for my kids.
If you want a math tutor, tell me.
I'll get you one
even if I have to take out a loan.
Then give me 1.5 million won.
1.5 million?
Whatever.
I'm the only one thinking about you.
I'm not doing this anymore.
Have Ju-young do it.
Ju-kyung, where are you going?
Hey, how was your first day?
I was a mess.
I'll learn things
and do better moving forward.
Why do you sound so down?
Are you outside?
Yes.
I came out to clear my head.
Do you want to come here?
I feel better after exercise.
You do? So how do I do it?
Grab me by my collar.
I'll grab the sleeve here, and then here.
Step in.
Hey.
Grabbing it.
Great job.
Now flip me over
using what you just learned.
How can I possibly flip you over?
If you succeed, I'll grant you a wish.
Really? You're not lying?
- Why would I lie to you?
- All right.
You come here!
Yay, I did it!
Wasn't that cheating?
I just learned.
You need to cut me some slack.
All right.
What's your wish?
My wish?
You can ask me to pay
for the beauty school course.
What? It's super expensive.
Even if it is.
Are you showing off that you're rich?
- Come on, tell me.
- Someone's watched some stuff.
No, thank you.
I got one.
What is it?
Well…
It's a bit embarrassing.
You know what? Never mind.
I'll go get changed.
LEE SOO-HO
The person you are trying to reach
is unavailable…
Why did you text…
BOYFRIEND
GIRLFRIEND
On my phone,
I saved your number as "Boyfriend."
It must have sprinkled.
It must have.
We don't have an umbrella.
We could have gotten soaked.
Lucky us, I guess.
- Are you all right?
- That was some bad luck.
What are you doing?
Sorry?
Aren't you coming up?
I'm coming.
Wait here. I'll get you some clothes.
Okay.
- Want to eat food?
- We could watch TV…
- Want to watch TV?
- Let's eat.
Let's eat.
You haven't had dinner yet, right?
I can make you…
Or should we just get delivery?
Sure.
I'm good with anything.
- Is pizza okay?
- Yes.
What is it?
Hey, what is this room?
- What?
- It's just locked so well.
Did you hide something weird in there?
It's not like that.
Are there some corpses inside
like in the movies?
Do you want to see it?
The passcode has been verified.
Are you a musician then?
I wanted to be one before.
What about now?
After what happened to Se-yeon,
I just couldn't.
It was Se-yeon…
who taught me how to write music.
It was hard to look at,
so I rarely came into this room.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have…
But it feels okay.
Maybe because you're with me.
Should we tell people that we go out?
Why all of a sudden?
You wanted to keep it a secret.
I feel like I pushed things my way
without even asking your opinion.
- What if you get dragged to the rooftop?
- Guess I'll let them.
I don't care either way.
It doesn't change the fact
that you're my girlfriend.
The song you played me before,
the unreleased song.
Did you write it?
Yes.
The lyrics were…
written by Se-yeon.
I see.
The song was really good.
Do you want me to play it?
Yes.
I quit playing the piano
while learning the first volume of Beyer.
I haven't played in a while either,
so don't hold your breath.
That noise was from outside.
Is it going to rain?
I can hear the thunder.
I wonder what's going on.
This piano sounds amazing.
It's expensive, right?
I'll go get it right away.
Wait.
Jeez, for crying out loud!
Thank you. Enjoy!
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
I thought I might clean the place for him,
but it's spotless.
There's nothing to…
What's this liquor bottle doing here
at a young student's place?
Gosh, this is expensive stuff.
It might have gone bad.
Trying it is the only way to know.
Soo-ho, I'll just have a taste, okay?
Just a pinch.
Want to watch a movie while we eat?
Sure.
It smells good.
What should we watch?
Well,
how about a horror movie?
We could watch something else.
Why? You can't watch scary stuff?
It rained and all, so maybe we can
watch a musical or something.
What? You, the horror comic nerd,
can't watch horror movies?
I already read them as comics every day,
so no need to watch them as movies, right?
It'll be okay.
I'll cover your eyes if you get scared.
I'm not that much of a wimp, okay?
Turn off the lights.
Lights off for horror movies.
There are other interesting…
I'm being such a nuisance
when he's on a date with his girlfriend.
- Here.
- Okay.
Soo-ho is a man, indeed.
You really haven't seen horror films,
have you?
Ghosts don't come out
in these kinds of scenes.
You said they don't come out.
Dad?
- I miss you.
- Me too.
Since when did you start going out?
Why didn't you tell me?
Me and Han Seo-jun?
By the way, Ju-kyung,
should I tell him how I feel
when I give him this?
Have you ever liked the same girl
as your best friend?
No!
Why are you two coming in together?
Don't people usually show their boyfriends
old photo albums when they come over?
I don't like you two talking,
much less locking eyes.
- Then we can't see each other?
- Lee Soo-ho!
Subtitle translation by: Sun-young Ahn